A Guide to the Governor's Employee Survey of the Virginia Dept. of Human Resource Management, 1998-2000.
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Governor's Employee Survey of the Virginia Dept. of Human Resource Management,
1998-2000.
The Library of Virginia
51257, 53457
Virginia. Dept. of Human Resource Management
4 cu. ft. (4 boxes)
These records are part of the Department of Human Resource Management record group (RG# 9)
This collection has been processed using minimal processing standards: the original arrangement has been maintained, the container list is brief and simple, and the records have not been refoldered and fasteners have not been removed.
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession 51257 was transferred by the Dept. of Human Resource Management, 2014 Mar 27
Accession 53457 was transferred by the Dept. of Human Resource Management, 2021 Nov 3
Virginia. -- Dept. of Human Resource Management
Employee-management relations in government -- Virginia.
Personnel management -- Virginia.
Surveys. -- aat.
Correspondence (letters). -- aat.
State government records -- Virginia. -- aat.
Virginia. Governor (1998-2002: Gilmore)
Contains material relating to Governor James Gilmore's survey of state government employees in 1998. Includes a sampling of surveys completed by state government employees, as well as correspondence relating to the execution of the survey and material relating to town hall meetings held in conjunction with the survey, town hall meeting videos, briefing books and final summary.
Contents List
- Governor's employee survey records (Accession 51257), 1998-2000., Extent: 3 cu. ft. (3 boxes).
  Arranged in original order.
  - Sample surveys (43100-44599), 1998 (Box 1)
  - Special file (surveys), 1998 (Box 2)
  - Commonwealth Currents, 1998-2000 (Box 2)
  - Survey results, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Survey categories, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Survey open ended questions, 19 (Box 2)
  - Verity information server, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Special project coding, undated (Box 2)
  - Data entry, 1998-1999 (Box 2)
  - Topics and agencies, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Test summary, undated (Box 2)
  - Open ended questions, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1998-2000 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence (binder), 1999 June-2000 Sept (Box 2)
  - Town Hall meetings - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Town Hall meetings - Results, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Town Hall meetings - Topic list sorted by agency, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Town Hall meetings - Employee questions, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Town Hall meetings - Comments, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Town Hall meetings - Commonwealth Current, 2000 Oct (Box 3)
  - Town Hall meetings - General, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Town Hall meetings - Video recording (VHS) - Roanoke, 1998 Sept 23 (Box 3)
  - Town Hall meetings - Video recording (VHS) - Annandale, 1998 Sept 24 (Box 3)
  - Town Hall meetings - Video recording (VHS) - Norfolk, 1998 Sept 24 (Box 3)
  - Town Hall meetings - Video recording (VHS) - Richmond, 1998 Sept 25 (Box 3)
- Governor's employee survey records (Accession 53457), 1998., Extent: 1 cu. ft. (1 box).
  - Governor Gilmore's Employee Survey Final Summary and Statistics (Data tables, v. 1), 1998 Dec (Box 1)
  - Governor Gilmore's Employee Survey Final Summary and Statistics (Data tables, v. II), 1998 Dec (Box 1)
  - Governor's briefing binder - Employee Town Hall meetings, 1998 Sept (Box 1)
  - Town Hall meeting - Roanoke (Video recording, VHS), 1998 Sept 23 (Box 1)
  - Town Hall meeting - Annandale (Video recording, VHS), 1998 Sept 24 (Box 1)
  - Town Hall meeting - Norfolk (Video recording, VHS), 1998 Sept 24 (Box 1)
  - Town Hall meeting - Richmond (Video recording, VHS), 1998 Sept 25 (Box 1)